coplogic.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy | LexisNexis Risk Solutions

### 4.1 Your Organization

If you access the Service through a subscription administered by your organization, your personal information and certain usage data gathered through the Service may be accessed by or shared with the administrators authorized by your organization for the purposes of usage analysis, subscription management and compliance, cost attribution and departmental budgeting. 

### 4.2 Application Licensor

If you access a third-party application on the Service through a license agreement with the licensor of that application, personal information relevant to that application will be shared with the licensor so that it can provide you access to the application, subject to the terms of its license agreement and privacy policy. 

### 4.3 Our Group Companies and Service Providers

Depending on the Service provided, we share personal information with:

  * Our affiliates, trading names and divisions within the LexisNexis Risk Solutions group of companies worldwide (for a list, [click here](https://risk.lexisnexis.com/contact-us#office-locations)) and certain RELX Group companies that provide technology, customer service and other shared services functions; and/or 
  * Our service providers, suppliers, agents and representatives, including but not limited to, payment processors, customer support, email service providers, IT service providers, mailing houses and shipping agents; 

to process the information as necessary to provide the Service, complete a transaction or fulfill your request or otherwise on our behalf based on our instructions and in compliance with this privacy policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

### 4.4 Your Choices

We share your personal information with our affiliates and with sponsors, joint venture partners and other third parties, including entities for which we are acting as an agent, licensee, application host or publisher, that wish to send you information about their products and services that may be of interest to you, as determined by your choices in managing your communications preferences and other settings. The Service may let you post and share personal information, comments, materials and other content. Any such contributions you disclose publicly may be collected and used by others, may be indexed by search engines, and might not be able to be removed. Please be careful when disclosing personal information in these public areas. 

### 4.5 For Legal Reasons

We also will disclose your personal information if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to: 

  * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or other legal obligation; 
  * detect, investigate and help prevent security, fraud or technical issues; and/or 
  * protect the rights, property or safety of LexisNexis Risk Solutions, our users, employees or others;

and as part of a corporate transaction, such as a transfer of assets or an acquisition by or merger with another company.
